Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[Reborn from the Ashes]
[الولادة من الرماد]
[Episode 25]
[الحلقة 25]
I falsely accuse you?
هل أتّهمك زوراً؟
Wanyan Jin, since you're so jealous,
وانيان جين، بما أنك تشعر بالغيرة الشديدة،
I'll let you have your fill this time.
سأتركك تشبع هذه المرة.
My Lord,
يا سيدي،
a jealous man is destined to be abandoned.
الرجل الغيور مصيره الهجر.
Be quiet.
كن هادئاً.
I'm still upset.
ما زلت منزعجاً.
I was wrong.
كنت مخطئاً.
But you have to promise me,
لكن عليك أن تعدني،
stay away from Prince Han.
ابتعد عن الأمير هان.
I don't like him.
أنا لا أحبه.
You say you're not jealous.
تقول إنك لست غيوراً.
Who in the world doesn't like you?
من في العالم لا يحبك؟
Today it's Prince Han,
اليوم هو الأمير هان،
tomorrow another man will be after you.
غداً سيلاحقك رجل آخر.
Do I have to worry every moment
هل عليّ أن أقلق في كل لحظة؟
that you will be taken away?
هل سيتم أخذك بعيدًا؟
Do you really think I'm such a fickle woman?
هل تعتقد حقاً أنني امرأة متقلبة المزاج إلى هذا الحد؟
Even if Prince Han
حتى لو كان الأمير هان
is more handsome than you,
هو أكثر وسامة منك،
richer than you,
أغنى منك،
I am still your wife.
ما زلت زوجتك.
Say that again.
قل ذلك مرة أخرى.
More handsome than you,
أكثر وسامة منك،
richer than you.
أغنى منك.
He is more handsome than you.
هو أكثر وسامة منك.
Why did you lure me here with the account book?
لماذا استدرجتني إلى هنا بدفتر الحسابات؟
Can't we just have a proper talk?
ألا يمكننا فقط إجراء محادثة حقيقية؟
Speak.
يتكلم.
What exactly do you want?
ماذا تريد بالضبط؟
I want
أريد
you dead.
أنت ميت.
Someone!
شخص ما!
Save my child!
أنقذوا طفلي!
Yi, are you alright?
يي، هل أنت بخير؟
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
please save our child.
أرجوكم أنقذوا طفلنا.
Stop right there!
توقف هنا!
Bring the physician here.
أحضر الطبيب إلى هنا.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
Qingran didn't push me on purpose.
لم تدفعني تشينغران عن قصد.
I was careless myself.
كنتُ أنا أيضاً مهملاً.
Feiyi! Hurry up!
فييي! أسرع!
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
the child is lost.
الطفل تائه.
What?
ماذا؟
Qingran,
كينغران،
you have quite the nerve.
لديك جرأة كبيرة.
Knowing Feiyi is pregnant,
مع العلم أن فييي حامل،
yet you still invited her to the pavilion.
ومع ذلك، فقد دعوتها إلى الجناح.
If she hadn't informed me before coming,
لو لم تكن قد أبلغتني قبل مجيئها،
did you really think you could get away with it?
هل ظننت حقاً أنك ستفلت بفعلتك؟
I didn't push her.
لم أضغط عليها.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
since this child has no ties to us,
بما أن هذا الطفل لا تربطه بنا أي صلة،
there's no need to press the matter further.
لا داعي للضغط على هذا الأمر أكثر من ذلك.
Nonsense.
هراء.
Someone!
شخص ما!
Take her away.
خذها بعيداً.
Hit her 20 times with a cane.
اضربها عشرين مرة بالعصا.
Lock her up in the prison.
اسجنوها في السجن.
Yes.
نعم.
I'll walk there myself.
سأذهب إلى هناك بنفسي.
Feiyi.
فييي.
I was only away from home for three days,
لم أغب عن المنزل إلا لثلاثة أيام فقط.
and you already got into trouble.
وقد وقعت في مشكلة بالفعل.
Su Feiyi used the account book to trap me.
استخدمت سو فييي دفتر الحسابات للإيقاع بي.
That's how it ended up like this.
هكذا انتهى الأمر على هذا النحو.
Think carefully. Was there anything strange back then?
فكر جيداً. هل كان هناك أي شيء غريب في ذلك الوقت؟
How dare they bully my woman while I was away?
كيف يجرؤون على مضايقة زوجتي أثناء غيابي؟
I'll make sure they all pay the price.
سأحرص على أن يدفعوا جميعاً الثمن.
I've figured it out.
لقد فهمت الأمر.
Young Master,
السيد الشاب،
I saw the truth behind the pavilion that day.
لقد رأيت الحقيقة وراء الجناح في ذلك اليوم.
Su Feiyi framed the crown princess.
قامت سو فييي بتلفيق التهمة لولي العهد.
She deliberately caused her own fall and miscarriage.
لقد تسببت عمداً في سقوطها وإجهاضها.
I originally wanted to testify for the crown princess.
كنت أرغب في الأصل أن أدلي بشهادتي لصالح ولية العهد.
But His Highness was so intimidating. I dared not speak the truth.
لكن سموه كان مخيفاً للغاية. لم أجرؤ على قول الحقيقة.
Su Feiyi,
سو فييي,
how dare you treat us like fools?
كيف تجرؤون على معاملتنا كالحمقى؟
I have completed the task.
لقد أنجزت المهمة.
You may leave now.
يمكنك المغادرة الآن.
Su Feiyi...
سو فيي...
Wen Yueqian?!
وين يويه تشيان؟!
You...
أنت...
How did you...
كيف عرفت...
Do you want to ask
هل تريد أن تسأل
how did I return from the underworld?
كيف عدت من العالم السفلي؟
Of course, it is for three matters.
بالطبع، يتعلق الأمر بثلاثة أمور.
First,
أولاً،
the grudge of disfigurement.
ضغينة التشويه.
Second,
ثانية،
the hatred of eye gouging.
كراهية فقء العيون.
No!
لا!
Third,
ثالث،
the pain of bloodletting.
ألم إراقة الدماء.
Just keep waiting,
استمر في الانتظار،
waiting for your blood
في انتظار دمك
to run dry.
ليجف.
Then all of this will be over.
ثم سينتهي كل هذا.
Yueqian,
يويهتشيان،
I was wrong.
كنت مخطئاً.
Wen Yueqian, I was wrong.
وين يويتشيان، كنت مخطئاً.
What mistake did you make?
ما الخطأ الذي ارتكبته؟
I shouldn't have deceived you to take your pure Yang blood.
ما كان ينبغي لي أن أخدعك لأخذ دمك اليانغ النقي.
I shouldn't have been unfaithful with Su Feiyi.
ما كان ينبغي لي أن أخون سو فايي.
I shouldn't have gouged out your eyes,
ما كان ينبغي لي أن أفقأ عينيك،
ruined your face, or endangered your life.
أفسد وجهك، أو عرّض حياتك للخطر.
I should never
لا ينبغي لي أبداً
have gotten Su Feiyi pregnant.
تسبب في حمل سو فييي.
I was wrong.
كنت مخطئاً.
But sadly, there's no cure for regret.
لكن للأسف، لا يوجد علاج للندم.
A mistake is a mistake.
الخطأ يبقى خطأً.
Just go ahead and regret it slowly.
انطلق وندم ببطء.
Wen Yueqian, please don't kill me.
وين يويتشيان، أرجوك لا تقتلني.
Qi,
تشي،
make sure you clearly see who I really am.
تأكد من أنك ترى بوضوح من أنا حقًا.
Su Qingran.
سو تشينغران.
Just now...
الآن...
You scoundrel!
يا وغد!
Confess everything.
اعترف بكل شيء.
Before,
قبل،
I went through so much to find pure Yang blood for you.
لقد مررت بالكثير لأجد لك دم يانغ نقي.
Yet you,
لكن أنت،
for Su Feiyi,
لسو فييي،
killed Wen Yueqian.
قُتل وين يويتشيان.
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.dramacool.club دعم الإدارة)
And now,
والآن،
you're scheming with her again,
أنت تتآمر معها مجدداً،
joining forces to deceive me.
يتحدون لخداعي.
I was framed as well.
لقد تم تلفيق التهمة لي أيضاً.
Go guard the tomb.
اذهب واحرس القبر.
Don't ever come back.
لا تعود أبداً.
I know my mistake.
أعرف خطئي.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Your Highness, don't do this.
يا صاحب السمو، لا تفعل هذا.
Qi is too fragile.
الطاقة الحيوية (تشي) هشة للغاية.
He just can't take it.
إنه ببساطة لا يستطيع تحمل ذلك.
It's all Su Feiyi's fault.
كل ذلك خطأ سو فييي.
She must have seduced Qi.
لا بد أنها أغوت تشي.
Hmph.
همم.
Since you feel sorry for him,
بما أنك تشعر بالشفقة عليه،
then go with him.
ثم اذهب معه.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Still making a scene here.
لا يزالون يثيرون ضجة هنا.
Su Feiyi,
سو فييي,
you really treat me like a fool.
أنت حقاً تعاملني كالأحمق.
Someone!
شخص ما!
Demote Su Feiyi to slave status
خفض رتبة Su Feiyi إلى حالة العبد
and throw her out of the Mansion.
وأطردها من القصر.
Your Highness, I didn't do it.
يا صاحب السمو، لم أفعل ذلك.
They're framing me.
إنهم يدبرون لي مكيدة.
Don't forget my original intention.
لا تنسوا نيتي الأصلية.
Silence.
الصمت.
I will handle
سأتولى الأمر.
today's matter myself.
أنا من أهتم بشؤون اليوم.
You all go back first.
ارجعوا جميعاً أولاً.
Su Feiyi,
سو فييي,
I can refrain from demoting you to slave status,
بإمكاني الامتناع عن إنزالك إلى مرتبة العبد،
but you can no longer stay here.
لكن لا يمكنك البقاء هنا بعد الآن.
Pack your things.
جهز أغراضك.
In a few days,
في غضون أيام قليلة،
I will send someone to escort you away.
سأرسل شخصاً ليرافقك بعيداً.
The wealth and honor you desire,
الثروة والشرف اللذان ترغب فيهما،
I will give it to you.
سأعطيك إياه.
Don't bring up the account book ever again.
لا تذكر دفتر الحسابات مرة أخرى.
Yes.
نعم.
The most dangerous place
أخطر مكان
[Military Supplies Ledger] is the safest place.
[سجل الإمدادات العسكرية] هو المكان الأكثر أمانًا.
These fools still can't found it.
هؤلاء الحمقى ما زالوا عاجزين عن إيجاده.
You all...
أنتم جميعاً...
♪In this world, who exactly♪
♪في هذا العالم، من بالضبط♪
♪Pushed me into the abyss?♪
♪دفعني إلى الهاوية؟♪
♪The sky is silent, and the sea says nothing♪
السماء صامتة، والبحر لا ينطق بكلمة.
♪Who shows me mercy in this world?♪
من يرحمني في هذا العالم؟
♪Cold winds sweep across the wasteland♪
♪ تهبّ رياح باردة على الأرض القاحلة ♪
♪Mercilessly gifting me snow and frost♪
♪يمنحني بلا رحمة الثلج والصقيع♪
♪In this fleeting life♪
♪في هذه الحياة الزائلة♪
♪No mercy, no answers♪
♪لا رحمة، لا إجابات♪
♪Yet one lamp shines, unafraid to go out♪
♪ومع ذلك، لا يزال مصباح واحد يضيء، غير خائف من الانطفاء♪
♪Time can twist, but people aren't perfect♪
قد يتغير الزمن، لكن البشر ليسوا كاملين.
♪Who decides who comes and who parts?♪
♪من يقرر من يأتي ومن يرحل؟♪
♪It all rests on a single hopeful thought♪
♪كل شيء يعتمد على فكرة واحدة تبعث على الأمل♪
♪Why fear one last breath?♪
♪لماذا نخشى اللحظة الأخيرة؟♪
♪Love is brief, full of regrets♪
♪الحب قصير، مليء بالندم♪
♪I paint the sky as a fan♪
أرسم السماء كالمروحة
♪To blow away nightmares and scatter the dust♪
♪لإزالة الكوابيس وتبديد الغبار♪
♪Can't resist the fate of being separated♪
لا أستطيع مقاومة مصير الفراق.
♪By distance♪
♪عن طريق المسافة♪
[Exclusive content rights reserved]
[جميع الحقوق محفوظة]
[by Youku Information Technology (Beijing) Co., Ltd.]
[من شركة Youku Information Technology (Beijing) Co., Ltd.]